没有
No.
你姐姐自杀之前大约一周
About a week before your sister took her life...
你是做什么职业的
what were you doing for a living then?
我是老师
I was a teacher.
这话太谦虚了吧
You're being modest, aren't you?
你当时是波士顿大学的教授
You were a professor at Boston University...
是吗
isn't that right?
是的 是助理教授
Yes, well, Assistant Professor.
你教什么
And what'd you teach?
哲学
Philosophy.
事实和逻辑 这方面内容的吧
Truth and logic. That sort of thing.
你的律师说你收养玛丽
Your attorney said that the primary reason...
主要原因是你姐姐
that you took Mary is because it was what your sister...
希望你这么做 这是事实吗
would have wanted you to do. Is that the truth?
是的
Yes.
那么黛安以前来过Pinellas县?
So Diane had visited Pinellas County before?
没有
No.